

### **Davi Roberto**

**Frontend Engineer** 

#### **About Me**

Hi there! My name is Davi Roberto, I really like music, reading and technology. I work with systems development for more than 10

years, and for 8 years with frontend.

I'm a frontend software engineer, I'm always looking for execution area and execution capacity.

29 Age

davifsroberto@outlook.com E-mail

Phone +353 89 478 4620

WhatsApp Click here

LinkedIn

GitHub

linkedin.com/in/davifsroberto github.com/davifsroberto

Site davifsroberto.github.io

#### Some Skills

UX and UI Angular Tests (unitary, behavior, e2e) React **TypeScript** Agile Methodologies

### **Experience**

#### Principal Frontend Engineer at Banco BV

April, 2022 | Present

Development of web applications with the Angular framework. During development, I am always aware of good practices to follow a high level of code standard, and in development with tests. It also helps less experienced developers on a day-to-day basis to technically evolve together and deliver a highly scalable project.

### Principal Frontend Engineer at Mottu

September, 2021 - April, 2022 | 7 mos

I develop forward delivery applications, backoffice applications and self-service totems. I always pay attention to development with tests, performance and best practices. I help less experienced developers, and work on restructuring old projects to a scalable frontend architecture. When necessary, I create the interfaces without relying on a UI designer. I have UI/UX notions and I like the subject.

#### Principal Frontend Engineer at Rommanel

October, 2020 - December, 2021 | 1 yr e 3 mos

Using the Angular framework, I develop systems for web and mobile completely, dealing with issues of security, performance, UI/UX, application architecture, modularization and the like. Always using good development practices and agile methodologies. Also dealing with the main types of tests such as: automated tests, unit tests, integration and e2e. It also helped colleagues who had less knowledge in web development.

# Frontend Engineer at Cielo

October, 2019 - October, 2020 | 1 yr e 1 mos

Development of systems for the financial area, creation of dashboards, applications that monitor services and generate reports on instabilities of financial transaction services. Some technologies I used: Angular 2+, React, UI/UX, Sass, Bootstrap, Agile Scrum.

# Web Developer Full Stack at Grupo Fast Solutions

July, 2017 - October, 2019 | 2 yrs e 4 mos

Analyze and develop web systems for large corporations, always focusing on solutions for the customer and their business needs, involving issues such as high code quality standards, performance, security and user experience. Some technologies I used in this process:

Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, JavaScript, ECMAScript 6+, jQuery, JSON, VueJS, Angular, UX, Photoshop, WebPack. Back-End: .NET, ASP.NET CORE, C#, SQL Server, Dapper, Entity Framework Core.

General: MVC, MVVM, TFS, GitHub, SEO, WEB API, SPA, Componentização, NPM, REST, JWT, P.O.O, Agile(Scrum).

#### Frontend Developer at Deevo Studio January, 2015 - December, 2016 | 2 yrs

Having the possibility to work on other projects in parallel, I accepted the invitation to be part of the Deevo Studio development team and develop projects for the web. My focus was to develop institutional websites and CMS using Wordpress. Some technologies that use Deevo Studio: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript/jQuery, PHP, WordPress, MySQL, Git.

#### Web Developer at Inter.net Brasil January, 2016 - July, 2016 | 7 mos

Hired to work as an intern for 6 months, I worked as a web developer, focused on the company's clients' website working with back-end and front-end.

# Frontend Developer at Soyuz Sistemas

July, 2015 - January, 2016 | 7 mos

Hired to work as an intern for 6 months, I worked as a web developer, focused on the company's clients' website working with front-end.

# **Education**

Bachelor's Degree in Internet Systems at Centro Universitário Senac (Brazil)

Develop totally original applications and also use others ready for implementation in new structures. Create and execute projects for the

various web vehicles, with discernment and balance between needs, both in interactive projects for the web and mobile devices.

# Contatos

LinkedIn

F-mail davifsroberto@outlook.com

+353 89 478 4620 Telefone WhatsApp Click here

linkedin.com/in/davifsroberto GitHub github.com/davifsroberto Site davifsroberto.github.io